Preliminary Guide to the Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art, 1960s-2000s SPEC.CGA.JGS
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Serbin, Walter, 1989-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 82)
- Serdarevic, Senaid, 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 83)
- Serdu, Serge Duhayon, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 84)
- Serebryakov, M., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 85)
- Sergei, Ainu Toinov, 1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 86)
- Sergey, Mosienko, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 87)
- Sergey, S., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 88)
- Sergisi, Anma, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 89)
- Sergiu, Nicola, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 90)
- Serguei, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 91)
- Serre, 1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 92)
- Seth, Vijay N., 1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 93)
- Seuss, Dr., 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 94)
- Sevcsik, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 11, Folder 95)
- Shabanov, Alexander, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 96)
- Shafeek, Salah, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 97)
- Shakirov, Yusup, 1992-1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 98, Box JGS 19, Folder 87)
- Shanks, Gene, 1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 99)
- Shapiro, Jonathan (Zapiro), 1988-1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 100)
- Sharkey, Michael, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 11, Folder 101)
- Sharon, Ariel, 1987 (Box JGS 11, Folder 102)
- Sheps, Yefim, 1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 103)
- Sherman, Goddard, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 104)
- Shevchik, John, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 105)
- Shi-Ying, Gao, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 106)
- Shields, Joseph, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 11, Folder 107)
- Shiller, Jay, 1997 (Box JGS 11, Folder 108)
- Shilov, Viacheslav, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 109)
- Shulyk, Guy, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 110)
- Sidorenko, Alexander, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 111)
- Sierra, Oscar, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 112)
- Sigitas, Burneckis, 1989-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 113)
- Silva, Loredano, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 114)
- Silver, Yvette J., 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 115)
- Simak, Juri, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 116)
- Simensky, Linda, 1996 (Box JGS 11, Folder 117)
- Simon, John, 1998 (Box JGS 11, Folder 118)
- Simon, Mark, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 119)
- Simon, Rainer, 1985-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 120)
- Simonson, Bill, 1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 121)
- Simpson, Randy, 1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 122)
- Sims, David, 1990 (Box JGS 11, Folder 123)
- Sinchinov, Evgeniy, 1987-1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 124)
- Sinclair, Pete, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 11, Folder 125)
- Singer, Phillip, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 126)
- Siro (Pierre Rollot), undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 127)
- Sirois, Alain, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 128)
- Sivanand, Mohan, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 11, Folder 129)
- Skauge, Hallvard, 1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 130)
- Skopintsev, V., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 131)
- Sliva, 1985-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 88, Box JGS 11, Folder 132)
- Smal, Oleg, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 133)
- Smallwood, S., 1991 (Box JGS 11, Folder 134)
- Smirnow, Igor, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 135)
- Smith, Geoffrey, undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 136)
- Smith, Harold A., 1978-1986 (Box JGS 11, Folder 137)
- Smith, James, 1995 (Box JGS 11, Folder 138)
- Smith, Kevin F., 1994 (Box JGS 11, Folder 139)
- Soebijoto, H., undated (Box JGS 11, Folder 140)
- Sokolov, Alexander, 1992 (Box JGS 11, Folder 141)
- Solga, Oliver, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 1)
- Sommers, Dick, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 2)
- Sondermann, M., 1988-1991 (Box JGS 12, Folder 3)
- Song, Heng Kim, 1990-1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 4)
- Sopka, Ljubomir, 1993-1997 (Box JGS 12, Folder 5)
- Sourek, Emil, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 6)
- de Sousa, Osvaldo, 1992-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 89)
- Sovova, Sonja, 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 7)
- Spahr, Jurg, 1993-2002 (Box JGS 12, Folder 8)
- Spiegelman, Art, 1987 (Box JGS 12, Folder 9)
- Spooner, John, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 10)
- Springer, Frank, 1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 11)
- Srbljanin, Predrag, 1992-1997 (Box JGS 12, Folder 12)
- Staake, Bob, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 12, Folder 13)
- Stampone, John, 1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 14)
- Stankovic, B., 1991-1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 15)
- Stankulov, A.H., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 16)
- Stanley, Stephen, 1991 (Box JGS 12, Folder 17)
- Stantis, Scott, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 18)
- Staradyimov, V., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 19)
- Starlight, Joe, circa 1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 20)
- Stauber, Jules, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 21)
- Stayskal, Wayne, 1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 22)
- Steadman, Ralph, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 23)
- Steed, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 24)
- Stefanovic, Miro, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 25)
- Steidle, Bruno, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 26)
- Stein, Ed, 1986 (Box JGS 12, Folder 27)
- Stein, Uli, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 28)
- Steinberg, S., 1967 (Box JGS 12, Folder 29)
- Steiner, Peter, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 30)
- Steiner, Richard, 1989 (Box JGS 12, Folder 31)
- Stemmle, Tom, 1987 (Box JGS 12, Folder 32)
- Stepanoff, Jim, 1972-1985 (Box JGS 12, Folder 33)
- Stepanov, V., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 34)
- Stephanos, Dale, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 35)
- Stern, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 36)
- Stetson, Heidi, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 37)
- Stevens, John, 1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 38)
- Stieger, Heinz, 1985-1987 (Box JGS 12, Folder 39)
- Stinson, Bill, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 40)
- Stjernkuist, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 41)
- Stockmann (Vallot), 1990-1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 42)
- Stojanovic, M., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 43)
- Stok, Andrze, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 44)
- Stokes, Mark, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 45)
- Storozhuk, L., 1988-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 46)
- Storti, Travis, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 47)
- Stout, Terry, circa 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 48)
- Stout, W.M., 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 49)
- Stoutsenberger, 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 50)
- Stowell, Gordon, 1988-1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 51)
- Strackovski, S., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 52)
- Striepecke, Karl Gerd, 1991 (Box JGS 12, Folder 53)
- Strzyz, Klaus, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 90)
- Suarez, M.C., 1989 (Box JGS 12, Folder 54)
- Suchcicki, Mike, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 55)
- Sudarta, G.M., 1978-1985 (Box JGS 12, Folder 56)
- Summa, A.J., 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 57)
- Summers, Dana, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 58)
- Superbi, Achille, circa 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 59)
- Susuzlu, Alper, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 60)
- Suzuki, Yoshiji, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 61)
- Swain, David, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 62)
- Swan, Curt, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 63)
- Sykes, Mark (Maz), undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 64)
- Sylvia, Dean, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 65)
- Szabo, Joe, 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 66)
- Szabo, L.R., circa 1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 67)
- Szebenyi, A., 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 68)
- Szep, Paul, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 69)
- Szorady, Mark, 1984-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 70)
- Szur-Szabo, Jozsef, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 71)
- Tabaka, Malgorzata, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 72)
- Tabatabaei, M., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 73)
- Taha, Leslie, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 74)
- Tahara, Nobuhisa, 1989 (Box JGS 12, Folder 75)
- Tahara, Tohota, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 76)
- Tailang, Sudhir, 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 77)
- Tamblyn, Bud, 1986 (Box JGS 12, Folder 78)
- Tamas, Csaszar, 1986-1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 79)
- Tamashagaran, 1999 (Box JGS 12, Folder 80)
- Tanaka, Minoru, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 81)
- Tao, Liu Qing, circa 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 82)
- Tapa, Ibrahim, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 83)
- Tarnowski, Paul, circa 1988 (Box JGS 12, Folder 84)
- Tarpley, Marsha, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 85)
- Tarr, Paul, 1988 (Box JGS 12, Folder 86)
- Taru, Eugen, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 87)
- Tati, Hector, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 88)
- Tchaousov, Wasily (Tcheldon), undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 89)
- Teh-Yong, Chu, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 90)
- Teitsworth, L., 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 91)
- Tennant, Rich, 1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 92)
- Teodor, Nicolae, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 93)
- Tesler, Oleg, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 94)
- Tetievski, M., circa 1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 95)
- Tettamanti, Bela, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 96)
- Teubert, Gary, 1986 (Box JGS 12, Folder 97)
- Thaves, Bob, 1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 98)
- Themerson, Franciszka and Stefan, 1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 99)
- Theoret, Marcel, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 100)
- Therrien, Bob, 1992 (Box JGS 12, Folder 101)
- Thuss, Henk, 1991 (Box JGS 12, Folder 102)
- Tica, Remi, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 103)
- Tikerpae, Elle, 1986 (Box JGS 12, Folder 104)
- Tingley, Merle, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 105)
- Tkaczyk, Witold, 1966-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 91, Box JGS 12, Folder 106)
- Tobocman, Seth, 1988 (Box JGS 12, Folder 107)
- Todd, J.F., 1987-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 108)
- Tomaschoff, Jan, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 109)
- Tomorrow, Tom, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 110)
- Tomov, Valentin, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 111)
- Toos, A.J., 1987-1989 (Box JGS 12, Folder 112)
- Topor, Ronald, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 113)
- Trendafilov, I., undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 114)
- Trenholm, Zach, 1992-1997 (Box JGS 12, Folder 115)
- Trinidad, Corky, 1989 (Box JGS 12, Folder 116)
- Trojano, Lucio, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 12, Folder 117)
- Trudeau, Gary, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 118)
- Trujillano, Marco, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 12, Box JGS 12, Folder 119)
- Tsimbalistov, 1995 (Box JGS 12, Folder 120)
- Tsogbayar, S., 1989-1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 121)
- Tsogtbayar, S., 1992-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 92, Box JGS 12, Folder 122)
- Tsonev, Todor, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 123)
- Tsu, Lim Cheng, 1992-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 93)
- Tsvetkov, Ivailo, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 124)
- T'Ung, Chang, 1990 (Box JGS 12, Folder 125)
- Tunin, Sergey, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 126)
- Turgut, Erhan, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 12, Folder 127)
- Turhan, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 128)
- Turier, Claude, undated (Box JGS 12, Folder 129)
- Turner, Martyn, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 130, Box JGS 19, Folder 94)
- Turner, Mike, 1993 (Box JGS 12, Folder 131)
- Turner, Morrie, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 12, Folder 132)
- Tzonev, Todor, 1990-1996 (Box JGS 12, Folder 133)
- Ugyfel, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 1)
- Uluschak, Edd, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 2)
- Umerov, Igor, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 3)
- Undeger, Sema, 1984-1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 4)
- Underwood, Mike, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 5)
- Unger, Jim, circa 1988 (Box JGS 13, Folder 6)
- Unguraitis, Edmundus, 1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 7)
- Upton, Colin, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 8)
- Urbanowicza, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 9)
- Urheberrecht, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 10)
- Vadun, Chuck, 1986 (Box JGS 13, Folder 11)
- Vaduva-Baumann, Ion, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 12)
- Vahter, Kuulo, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 13)
- Vakhitov, Fareed, 1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 14)
- Valerry, Paul, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 15)
- Valiakhmetov, M., 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 16)
- Valk, Pol De (Brasser), undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 17)
- Vallot, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 18)
- Valter, Jano, 1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 19)
- van Dam, Arend, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 20)
- van Den Hanenberg, Patrick, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 21)
- van Der Keyl, Jim, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 22)
- van Gal, De Week, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 23)
- van Tetterode, Edo, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 24)
- van Vlack, M., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 25)
- Vander, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 26)
- Vanek, Jiri, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 27)
- Vanek, Marcel, 1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 28)
- Vansovich, Andrey, 1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 29)
- Vanstiphout, B., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 30)
- van Woerkom, 1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 31)
- Varchenko, Igor, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 32)
- Varhan, Nevzat, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 33)
- Varnas, Jonas, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 34)
- Varro, Sandor, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 35)
- Vartchenko, N., 1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 36)
- Vasar, Aarne, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 37)
- Vasilevski, Ane, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 95, Box JGS 13, Folder 38)
- Vasilovich, Guy, 1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 39)
- Veenenbos, Jean, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 40)
- Veitch, Rick, 1990-1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 41)
- Velarde, Omar Z., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 42)
- Veley, Bradford, 1985-1986 (Box JGS 13, Folder 43)
- Verlinden, J., 1986 (Box JGS 13, Folder 44)
- Vernon, Robert, 1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 45)
- Victor, Balabas, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 46)
- Vier, Jed, 1992-1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 47)
- Viktorovich, Malko, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 48)
- Villages, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 49)
- Vincke, Bob, 1996 (Box JGS 13, Folder 50)
- Vitello, Alan, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 51)
- Viviano, Sam, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 52)
- Viztes, E., 1987 (Box JGS 13, Folder 53)
- Vlaber, Vladimir Beresnev, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 54)
- Vladdo, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 13, Folder 55)
- Vlahovic, J., 1982-1996 (Box JGS 13, Folder 56)
- Voljevica, I., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 57)
- von Alten, Bruce, 1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 58)
- Voskarides, Sotos (Aipolides), 1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 59)
- Vuitton, Louis, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 60)
- Vybornov, I.V., 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 61)
- Vyjidak, A., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 62)
- Waalkes, Otto, 1989-1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 63)
- Wagner, Peter, 1987 (Box JGS 13, Folder 64)
- Wahl, Andrew, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 65)
- Wairkar, P., circa 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 66)
- Waite, Keith, 1985-1987 (Box JGS 13, Folder 67)
- Wakhitov, Farit, 1987-1994 (Box JGS 19, Folder 96, Box JGS 13, Folder 68)
- Walker, 1989-1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 69)
- Walker, Mort, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 13, Folder 70)
- Waller, Charles, 1988 (Box JGS 13, Folder 71)
- Wallmeyer, Dick, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 13, Folder 72)
- Wasserman, Dan, 1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 73)
- Watkins, David, circa 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 74)
- Watremez, E., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 75)
- Watson, A.N., 1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 76)
- Watterson, Bill, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 13, Folder 77)
- Way, Henning, 1985-1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 78)
- Weber, A.P., circa 1973 (Box JGS 13, Folder 79)
- John Weber, 1990 (Box JGS 19, Folder 97)
- Weber, Kurt, circa 1987 (Box JGS 13, Folder 80)
- Wei, He, 1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 81)
- Weinberg, Joshua, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 82)
- Weiss, Oliver, 1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 83)
- Weitz, Stephen, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 84)
- Wepman, Dennis, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 98)
- Werner, Charles, 1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 85)
- Westford, Hakan, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 86)
- Wetzel, Bert, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 13, Folder 87)
- White, Leo, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 88)
- Wicks, Randy, 1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 89)
- Wilkie, Bob, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 90)
- Wilkinson, Signe, 1990-1996 (Box JGS 13, Folder 91)
- Will, Andrzej, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 92)
- Willers, Terry, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 93)
- Williams, D., 1993-1997 (Box JGS 13, Folder 94)
- Wilson, Barry, 1987-1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 95)
- Wilson, Jeff, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 13, Folder 96)
- Wilson, Roy, 1976 (Box JGS 13, Folder 97)
- Winnik, L.T., circa 1985 (Box JGS 13, Folder 98)
- Winter, Mitch, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 99)
- Woerkom, A.V., circa 1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 100)
- Wokoszyn, J., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 101)
- Wolfe, George, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 102)
- Wonsoo, Yi, 1994-2004 (Box JGS 13, Folder 103)
- Wood, Art, 1987-1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 104)
- Woodman, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 105)
- Woon-Kyong, Jung, 1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 106)
- Wright, Dick, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 107)
- Wright, Don, 1988 (Box JGS 13, Folder 108)
- Wright, Larry, 1988-1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 109)
- Wuerker, Matt, circa 1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 110)
- Wysocki, K., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 111)
- Xiao, Ji Shi, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 112)
- Xu, Peng Fei, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 113)
- Yamamoto, I., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 114)
- Yamandi (No-Rio), undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 115)
- Yamanoi, Norio, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 116)
- Yanardag, S., 1994-1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 117)
- Yavuz, Kamil, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 118)
- Yao, Zheng Xin, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 119)
- Yayo, 1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 120)
- Yeh, Phil, 1986-1997 (Box JGS 13, Folder 121, Box JGS 19, Folder 99)
- Yehezkiyau, Nissim, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 122)
- Yerke, Geoff, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 123)
- Yeste, Diego, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 124)
- Yi, Jiang, circa 1995 (Box JGS 13, Folder 125)
- Yi, Liu, 1988 (Box JGS 13, Folder 126)
- Ykenga, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 127)
- Yoe, Craig, 1992 (Box JGS 13, Folder 128)
- Yoot, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 129)
- You-Sheng, J., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 130)
- Young, Chic A., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 131)
- Young, Dean, 1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 132)
- Young, Eddie, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 133)
- Yovev, Martin, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 134)
- Yrigoyen, Penny, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 13, Folder 135)
- Yuan-Lin, Huang, undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 136)
- Yuen, Emu, circa 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 137)
- Yuzhniy, Victor, 1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 138)
- Zainudin, undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 1)
- Zakir, undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 2)
- Zampier, Brian, 1991 (Box JGS 13, Folder 3)
- Zanco, M.L., 1990 (Box JGS 13, Folder 4)
- Zebrowski, L., undated (Box JGS 13, Folder 5)
- Zec, Milan, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 13, Folder 6)
- Ze'ev (Farkas), 1990-1996 (Box JGS 14, Folder 7)
- Zeichen, Rauch, 1999 (Box JGS 14, Folder 8)
- Zemunik, V., undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 9)
- Zervos, Petros, undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 10)
- Zhivutsky, G., 1993 (Box JGS 14, Folder 11)
- Zhmaylo, A., 1987-1991 (Box JGS 14, Folder 12)
- Ziaei, Masoud, 1995 (Box JGS 14, Folder 13)
- Ziafati, Majid, 1993 (Box JGS 14, Folder 14)
- Zibrat, Dinko, 1983-1989 (Box JGS 14, Folder 15)
- Zich, Lubomir, 1996 (Box JGS 14, Folder 16)
- Zidarov, V., 1991 (Box JGS 14, Folder 17)
- Ziehm, Howard, 1995 (Box JGS 14, Folder 18)
- Zimmerman, R., 1988 (Box JGS 14, Folder 19)
- Ziomecki, Z., undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 20)
- Zlatkovski, M., 1989-1996 (Box JGS 14, Folder 21, Box JGS 19, Folder 100)
- Zohdy, undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 22)
- Zong-Cheng, B.Y., undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 23)
- Zorad, Erno, undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 24)
- Zsofi, Varga, 1985 (Box JGS 14, Folder 25)
- Zu, Zola, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 14, Folder 26)
- Zunzi, 1991 (Box JGS 14, Folder 27)
- Archives, undated (Box JGS 14, Folder 28)
- Authorization for Publication, 1986-1990 (Box JGS 14, Folder 29)
- Bookfairs, 1990 (Box JGS 15, Folder 32)
- Business, 1985-1994 (Box JGS 15, Folder 33-34)
- Business Machines, 1986-1997 (Box JGS 15, Folder 34)
- Business Plan, 1982-2004 (Box JGS 15, Folder 35)
- Calendar, undated (Box JGS 17, Folder 13)
- Cartoon Aid, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 15, Folder 36)
- Coincidental Likenesses, circa 1988 (Box JGS 15, Folder 37)
- Complaints, 1989 (Box JGS 15, Folder 38)
- Contracts, 1990-2003 (Box JGS 15, Folder 39)
- Copyright, 1978-1990 (Box JGS 17, Folder 14)
- Covers #1, 1987 (Box JGS 17, Folder 15)
- Evaluations, 1987 (Box JGS 17, Folder 16)
- Flash Points, undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 61)
- Focus, undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 66)
- Form Letter, circa 1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 17)
- Foundations, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 17, Folder 18)
- Guidelines, undated (Box JGS 17, Folder 19)
- Human Rights, 1989-1995 (Box Jgs 17, Folder 20)
- International Competition, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 17, Folder 21)
- Johnson and Hayward, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 17, Folder 22)
- Legal Business, 1972-1999 (Box JGS 17, Folder 23)
- Letters, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 21, Folder 67)
- Libraries, 1987 (Box JGS 17, Folder 24)
- No Comment, 1988-1998 (Box JGS 21, Folder 68)
- Philadelphia Competition, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 17, Folder 25)
- Publishers Weekly, 1992 (Box JGS 21, Folder 63)
- Quotes on Witty World, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 17, Folder 26)
- Reagan, undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 64)
- Rex, undated (Box JGS 17, Folder 27)
- Speeches, undated (Box JGS 17, Folder 28)
- Stamps, undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 65)
- Statesmen, 1989 (Box JGS 17, Folder 29)
- Tax, 1987 (Box JGS 17, Folder 30)
- Tele-Art, 1990-1991 (Box JGS 21, Folder 57)
- Trademark, 1985 (Box JGS 17, Folder 31)
- U.S. Post Office, 1984-1988 (Box JGS 17, Folder 32)
- Valley Distributors, 1992 (Box JGS 21, Folder 59)
- Vladimir, 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 60)
- Ton Smits Huis, 1985-2003 (Box JGS 15, Folder 44)
- Watson-Guptill, 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 62)
- Basel, 1986-1999 (Box JGS 14, Folder 30)
- Beringen (Belgium), 1987-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 33)
- Boca Raton, 1986-1999 (Box JGS 15, Folder 31)
- Boechout (Belgium), 1994-2002 (Box JGS 17, Folder 34)
- Boom (Belgium), 1992-1994 (Box JGS 17, Folder 35)
- Bornem (Belgium), 1990 (Box JGS 17, Folder 36)
- Bruxelles (Belgium), 1986-1988 (Box JGS 17, Folder 37)
- Charleroi (Belgium), 1988-1992 (Box JGS 17, Folder 38)
- Edinburgh, 1989-1992 (Box JGS 17, Folder 39)
- Gabrovo (Bulgaria), 1988-1997 (Box JGS 17, Folder 40)
- La Habana (Cuba), 1991 (Box JGS 17, Folder 41)
- Hannover, 1992-1997 (Box JGS 15, Folder 40)
- Istanbul, 1987-1990 (Box JGS 15, Folder 41)
- Knokke-Heist (Belgium), 1989-1993 (Box JGS 17, Folder 42)
- Kruishoutem (Belgium), 1991 (Box JGS 17, Folder 43)
- London, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 15, Folder 42)
- Montreal, undated (Box JGS 17, Folder 44)
- New Westminster (British Columbia), 1991 (Box JGS 17, Folder 45)
- Olen (Belgium), 1989-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 46)
- Piaui (Brazil), 1991 (Box JGS 17, Folder 47)
- Piracicaba (Brazil), 1974-1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 48)
- Porto Alegre (Brazil), 1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 49)
- Rio Comics Convention (Brazil), 1991 (Box JGS 17, Folder 50)
- Rio de Janeiro, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 17, Folder 51)
- Sydney, 1993 (Box JGS 17, Folder 52)
- Zagreb, 1996 (Box JGS 17, Folder 53)
- San Francisco, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 15, Folder 43)
- Washington, 1965-1995 (Box JGS 15, Folder 45)
- Artist Files--A, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 1)
- Artist Files--B, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 2)
- Artist Files--C, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 3)
- Artist Files--D, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 4)
- Artist Files--E, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 5)
- Artist Files--F, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 6)
- Artist Files--G, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 7)
- Artist Files--H, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 8)
- Artist Files--I, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 9)
- Artist Files--J, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 10)
- Artist Files--K, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 11)
- Artist Files--L, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 12)
- Artist Files--M, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 13)
- Artist Files--N, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 14)
- Artist Files--O, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 15)
- Artist Files--PQ, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 16)
- Artist Files--R, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 17)
- Artist Files--S, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 18)
- Artist Files--T, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 19)
- Artist Files--U, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 20)
- Artist Files--V, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 21)
- Artist Files--W, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 22)
- Artist Files--XY, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 23)
- Artist Files--Z, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 24)
- Carrousel, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 25-27)
- Miscellaneous, undated (Box JGS 16, Folder 28)
- Agoura, undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 1)
- Albi (France), 1993-2000 (Box JGS 20, Folder 1)
- Algeria, 1985 (Box JGS 18, Folder 1)
- Amstelveen (Netherlands), 1989 (Box JGS 20, Folder 2)
- Ancona (Italy), 1988-1999 (Box JGS 20, Folder 3)
- Anglet, 1993-1996 (Box JGs 20, Folder 4)
- Angouleme, 1990-2002 (Box JGS 20, Folder 5)
- Ankara, 1995-1999 (Box JGS 21, Folder 2)
- Arequipa (Peru), 1992-2006 (Box JGS 21, Folder 3)
- Argentina, 1988-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 2)
- Athens, 1994 (Box JGS 20, Folder 6)
- Australia, 1985-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 3)
- Austria, 1985-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 4)
- Bangladesh, 1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 5)
- Barcelona, 1991 (Box JGS 21, Folder 4)
- Belgium, 1985-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 6)
- Berlin, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 20, Folder 9)
- Bjelovar, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 20, Folder 10)
- Bogota (Colombia), 1990-1991 (Box JGS 20, Folder 7)
- Bolivia, 1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 7)
- Bordighera (Italy), 1987-1997 (Box JGS 20, Folder 11)
- Brasilia, 1991 (Box JGS 20, Folder 8)